homes.com 2011-06-07

# Dominion Enterprises | Privacy Policy

| 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on this Web site. Please see our Terms and Conditions of Site Use for additional information applicable to use of our Web site.

**The Information We Collect**

You do not have to give us personally identifiable information in order to visit our Web site. However, on the Web site, you may be able to order products, enter contests, participate in a survey or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. Personally identifiable information is generally provided and collected when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. As a result of those actions, you may supply us with such information as your name, address, phone numbers, e-mail address, contact preferences, credit card information, financial information and information relating to a support or service issue that may, alone or in combination with other data, constitute personally identifiable information. If we collect personally identifiable information from you, you are giving us permission to use that information for the specific purpose for which it is provided and to contact you regarding site services, improve or enhance site performance, to offer you information regarding products and services, fulfill product orders, improve our Web site, to communicate to you about other matters that may be of interest to you and for any other purpose described in this Privacy Policy. In connection with the foregoing, we may share your information with our affiliates. Users unwilling to provide personally identifiable information online can choose to work with a sales representative or customer service representative to utilize member services or other site offerings. 

We also may collect, store and use certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). In addition, we aggregate data from multiple users in a manner that is not personally identifiable and use such data as we deem appropriate.

**How We Use the Information**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their commercial use. We share personally identifiable customer information with unaffiliated third parties only as described herein.

  * **Businesses We Do Not Control** : At times, we may provide products and services on our Web site in cooperation with an unaffiliated third party. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party. 
  * **Agents** : We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * **Promotional Offers** : Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. 
  * **Business Transfers** : As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy companies, subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that we are acquired or assigned, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 
  * **Protection of Our Web site and Others** : We reserve the right to release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Site Use and other agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of this company, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 
  * **With Your Consent** : Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to monitor user traffic patterns, analyze and quantify user preferences, improve the design and content of our Web site, and enable us to personalize your user experience. All such usage data shall be the exclusive property of this Web Site.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed or accessed by a third party in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

Dominion Enterprises, its parent, affiliates and licensees reserve the right to sell or disclose some personally identifiable information collected on our Web site to third parties whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases and non-profit organizations) that want to market products and services to you. If we share personally identifiable information, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses. Any right of the third party to distribute, transfer, transmit, disclose or resell the information is prohibited.

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products and services that may be of interest to you. If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this Web site, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this Web site.

Finally, this Web site will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

**Third Party Online Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to show you advertisements tailored to your interests on this and other Web sites and other interactive media and/or to keep track of your response to each ad. For more information on this practice, or to Opt-Out of having this information used by these companies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

To enhance your experience with our Web site, many of our Web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Web site. However, once you choose to furnish our Web site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our Web site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our Web site), save your password in password-protected areas and enable you to use shopping carts on our Web site. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services.

"Web beacons" or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a Web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a Web page. For example, Web beacons or similar technology can be used to count the users who visit a Web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use Web beacons or similar technology on this Web site from time to time for this and other purposes. 

In addition, when you visit our Web sites, third party vendors and advertisers also place or read cookies on your Internet browser. This is a common practice on the Internet; these cookies may be used to determine whether you have visited other Web sites, to measure the effectiveness of advertising and links on other Web sites, and to provide you with information of potential interest to you, among other purposes. This is not an exhaustive list of all uses of cookies on our Web sites.

Most Web browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can, however, set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. In addition, cookies can be easily and safely deleted from your system. See your browser's help section for instructions. To Opt-Out of this practice, or to obtain more information on cookies, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) for more information.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers and Sponsors**

Our Web Site may contain links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. While visiting this Web site, you may link to another Web site via a window opened within (or on top of) our Web site. Our privacy policies and procedures may or may not be consistent with the policies and procedures of other Web sites you visit while here. Users should consult, read and understand any other Web site’s privacy notices before choosing to provide personally identifiable data on such linked Web site as our privacy policies and treatment of your data does not apply and we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

This Web site sometimes may offer products, services or content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that are sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties typically have access to the personally identifiable information that you submit, if any, in connection with that offering in order to participate in such particular Web site activity. Dominion Enterprises, its parent, affiliates and licensees have no control over these third parties' use of this information. This Web site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

This Web site may use a third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see on our Web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, Web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

****Our Commitment to Security****

We have in place what we believe to be reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the personally identifiable information we collect and help prevent unauthorized access and use of such data.

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. To assist in keeping your personal information safe, you must use an SSL-enabled browser (i.e., Internet Explorer). 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. Additionally, change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure Web browser. 

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**

You may obtain information regarding the personally identifiable information that this Web site has collected about you online for the limited purpose of viewing and correcting any factual errors in such information. Access to personally identifiable information that is collected from our Web site may be accessible for a limited period of time from the point of collection. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our Web site, return to that portion of the Web site to review the information you provided.  Alternatively, you may send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting information about or corrections to your personally identifiable information **Dominion Enterprises, Intellectual Property Administrator, P.O. Box 2576, Norfolk, VA  23501 or [IPadministrator@dominionenterprises.com](mailto:IPadministrator@dominionenterprises.com)** **** subject to verification procedures. To protect your privacy and security, we will take commercially reasonable steps to help verify your identity before providing information, granting access or making corrections. 

****Usage Terms****

Access to and use of this Web site is subject to compliance with this Web site’s Terms of Use.

Unsubscribe Requests  
To unsubscribe from email communications, please enter your email address and select the name of the business from the list on our [Email Opt Out Form](http://www.dominionenterprises.com/main/do/DE_Email_Opt_Out_Form).

****Special Note for Parents****

The Web site you are visiting is our general audience Web site and was not designed for children. We are not responsible for any access or use of this Web site by children. This Web site does not sell products for purchase by children. 

****How to Contact Us****

If you have any questions or concerns about the online Privacy Policy for this Web site or its implementation, you may contact the **Dominion Enterprises Intellectual Property Administrator, P.O. Box 2576, Norfolk, VA  23501 or [IPadministrator@dominionenterprises.com](mailto:IPadministrator@dominionenterprises.com)** for information as to how to contact this Web site by e-mail.

****Updates and Effective Date****   
We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting, unless otherwise indicated. We have no duty or obligation to inform prior visitors that changes have been made, regardless of the scope and importance of the changes. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Web site after such changes are posted will be deemed to constitute your agreement to and acceptance of such changes.  
  
---|---
